A Guide to the Philip S. Hench Walter Reed Yellow Fever Collection 1806-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- LETTER FRAGMENT FROM WALTER REED N.D., AL FRAGMENT (P) (Box-folder 142-056)
- LETTER FRAGMENT FROM WALTER REED N.D., AL FRAGMENT (P) (Box-folder 142-057)
- LETTER FRAGMENT FROM WALTER REED N.D., AL FRAGMENT (P) (Box-folder 142-058)
- LETTER FRAGMENT FROM WALTER REED N.D., AL FRAGMENT (P), NEGATIVE IMAGE (Box-folder 142-059)
- LETTER FRAGMENT FROM WALTER REED N.D., AL FRAGMENT (P), NEGATIVE IMAGE (Box-folder 142-060)
- LETTER FROM EMILIE LAWRENCE REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH N.D., ALS (Box-folder 142-061)
- LETTER FROM EMILIE LAWRENCE REED TO JAMES E. PEABODY N.D., ALS (P) WITH AN (Box-folder 142-062)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - NOTES REGARDING VISIT TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED AT BURLINGTON HOTEL, WASHINGTON, D.C. N.D., AMS (Box-folder 142-063)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - NOTES READING LETTERS FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED (HER FATHERS) IN BANK VAULT N.D., AN (Box-folder 142-064)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - DIAGRAM OF US GEN HOSP WASH BARRACKS 2ND FLOOR N.D., AN (Box-folder 142-065)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH N.D., ALS (Box-folder 142-066)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH N.D., CHRISTMAS CARD S WITH AA (Box-folder 142-067)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - NOTE LISTING MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS HELD IN HIS HOUSE SAFE N.D., AN (Box-folder 142-068)
- PAPER CUTTER PRESENTED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED MADE FROM WOOD FROM BIRTHPLACE OF WALTER REED N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 142-069)
- PIECE OF GREY PAPER N.D., MISCELLANY (Box-folder 142-070)
- TELEGRAM FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1943/05/13, TELEGRAM (AUTOGRAPH COPY) (Box-folder 142-071)
- TELEGRAM FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1943/05/13, TELEGRAM (AUTOGRAPH COPY P) WITH AA (Box-folder 142-072)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - STATEMENT REGARDING HIS PURCHASE OF LETTERS OF WALTER REED FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/04/24, TMS S WITH AA (Box-folder 142-073)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - STATEMENT REGARDING HIS PURCHASE OF LETTERS OF WALTER REED FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/04/24, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 142-074)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - STATEMENT REGARDING HIS PURCHASE OF LETTERS OF WALTER REED FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/04/24, TMS S (P) (Box-folder 142-075)
- CHECK FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/04/24, CHECK (Box-folder 142-076)
- CHECK FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/04/24, CHECK WITH VERSO (P) (Box-folder 142-077)
- TELEGRAM FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/04/24, TELEGRAM (Box-folder 142-078)
- TELEGRAM FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/04/24, TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 142-079)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/05/12, ALS WITH AA (Box-folder 142-080)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/05/12, ALS WITH AA (P) (Box-folder 142-081)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO CHARLES H. ROYCE 1965/09/13, TL (P) (Box-folder 142-082)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO CHARLES H. ROYCE 1965/09/21, TL (P) WITH AA (Box-folder 142-083)
- LETTER FROM THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MARY HENCH 1965/09/23, TL S (P) (Box-folder 142-084)
- LIST OF INSTITUTIONAL MANUSCRIPT COLLECTIONS COMPILED BY ANNE FREUDENBERG (WITH NOTES OF ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH) 1965/09/23, TMS WITH AA (P) (Box-folder 142-085)
- LETTER FROM [ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH] TO ROSE [s.n.] 1965/09/25, AN (Box-folder 142-086)
- LETTER FROM CHARLES H. ROYCE TO ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH 1965/09/26, ALS (P) WITH AA (Box-folder 142-087)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO MARY HENCH, PHILIP KAHLER HENCH, SUSAN KAHLER HENCH, AND JOHN BIXLER HENCH 1965/09/28, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 142-088)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO MARY HENCH, PHILIP KAHLER HENCH, SUSAN KAHLER HENCH, AND JOHN BIXLER HENCH 1965/09/28, TLS WITH AA (P) (Box-folder 142-089)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO MARY HENCH AND ROSE [s.n.] 1965/10/03, ANS (Box-folder 142-090)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO CHARLES H. ROYCE 1965/10/16, TLS (P) WITH AA, AN (Box-folder 142-091)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO CHARLES H. ROYCE 1965/10/16, TLS (P) WITH AA (Box-folder 142-092)
- LETTER FROM JOHN COOK WYLLIE TO MARY HENCH 1965/10/16, ALS (Box-folder 142-093)
- LETTER FROM ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH TO THOMAS h. HUNTER 1965/11/20, ALS (P) (Box-folder 142-094)
- ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH - NOTES DESIGNATING REED FAMILY AND LETTER OWNERSHIP CORRESPONDENCE 1965 CA., ANS (2) (Box-folder 142-095)
- EXTRACTS FROM THE RECORDS OF THE WAR DEPARTMENT OFFICE OF THE SURGEON GENERAL, REGISTER OF MEDICAL OFFICERS, VOLS. 6-11, REGARDING WALTER REED 1875-1902, AMD (P) NEGATIVE IMAGE (Box-folder 143-001)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED 1893/07/03, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 143-002)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO JOSEPH Y. PORTER 1894/01/19, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 143-003)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO THE SECRETARY OF WAR 1898/03/25, TL (CC), WITH AA (Box-folder 143-004)
- JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1899/05/25, ALS (Box-folder 143-005)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED, LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1899/06/05, 2 TLS (CC) (Box-folder 143-006)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG [1899]/05/25, ALS (Box-folder 143-007)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1899/07/10, ALS (Box-folder 143-008)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1899/07/12, ALS (Box-folder 143-009)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/03/27, ALS (Box-folder 143-010)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/04/01, ALS (Box-folder 143-011)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/04/08, ALS (Box-folder 143-012)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/04/26, ALS (Box-folder 143-013)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/06/13, ALS (Box-folder 143-014)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG [1900]/09/08, AL, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 143-015)
  A NEW MALARIA THEORY
- LETTER FROM HUGH L. SCOTT TO ARISTIDES A. AGRAMONTE 1900/09/20, TLS (P) (Box-folder 143-016)
- LETTER FROM LEONARD WOOD TO ARISTIDES A. AGRAMONTE 1900/09/22, TLS (P) (Box-folder 143-017)
- LETTER FROM LEONARD WOOD TO ARISTIDES A. AGRAMONTE 1900/09/22, TLS (P) (Box-folder 143-018)
- LETTER FROM ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE TO ERNST LEITZ AND WILLIAM KRAFFT 1900/10/05, ALS (P) (Box-folder 143-019)
- LETTER FROM ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE TO BAUSCH AND LOMB OPT. CO. 1900/10/05, ALS (P) (Box-folder 143-020)
- LETTER FROM T. STEINHART TO ARISTIDES A. AGRAMONTE 1900/10/18, TLS (P) (Box-folder 143-021)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/10/20, ALS (Box-folder 143-022)
- JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN - CHECKBOOK FOR THE EXPENSES OF THE U.S. ARMY YELLOW FEVER COMMISSION 1900/11/01-1901/12/03, CHECKBOOK WITH AA (Box-folder 143-023)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/11/05, ALS (Box-folder 143-024)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/11/09, ALS (Box-folder 143-025)
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 83 WITH ANNOTATION BY WILLIAM M. BRUMBY 1900/11/14, TMS WITH TNS (P), NEGATIVE IMAGE (Box-folder 143-026)
  CONCERNS ROGER POST AMES AND THE YELLOW FEVER COMMISSION
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG, LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/11/18-19, ALS (Box-folder 143-027)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/11/25, ALS (Box-folder 143-028)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/12/09, ALS (Box-folder 143-029)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1900/12/14, ALS WITH POSTAGE STAMPS (Box-folder 143-030)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED 1900/12/20, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 143-031)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG [1900]/12/23, ALS (Box-folder 143-032)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED 1900/12/27, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 143-033)
- DOCTOR JESSE W. LAZEAR DIES IN HAVANA (BALTIMORE SUN) 1900, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING WITH AA (Box-folder 143-034)
- JESSE W. LAZEAR, MABEL H. LAZEAR, BONNIE TRUBY, JOHN J. REPETTI, DR. DE POORTER AT CABANA FORTRESS, CUBA 1900, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 143-035)
- SURGEON GENERAL GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG ca. 1900, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 143-036)
- SURGEON GENERAL GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG ca. 1900, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 143-037)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/01/03, ALS (Box-folder 143-038)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/01/21, ALS (Box-folder 143-039)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/02/03, ALS (Box-folder 143-040)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/02/28, ALS (Box-folder 143-041)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/04/16, ALS (Box-folder 143-042)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/05/19, ALS (Box-folder 143-043)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/08/28, ALS (Box-folder 143-044)
- LETTER FROM LOUISE YOUNG KEAN TO MRS. MASON YOUNG 1901/12/07, ALS (Box-folder 143-045)
- MILITARY RECORD AND DISCHARGE OF JAMES L. HANBERRY 1901/12/12, PRINTED FORM WITH AA (P) (Box-folder 143-046)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO HOWARD A. KELLY 1902/12/12, ALS (Box-folder 143-047)
- LETTER FROM A. E. BATES TO ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1903/01/13, TLS WITH AA (P) (Box-folder 143-048)
- LETTER FROM ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1903/02/12, TL (P) (Box-folder 143-049)
- EXTRACTS OF STATEMENTS CONCERNING WALTER REED COMPILED AND PUBLISHED BY THE WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1903 CA., PAMPHLETS (2) WITH AA (Box-folder 143-050)
- EXTRACTS OF STATEMENTS CONCERNING WALTER REED COMPILED AND PUBLISHED BY THE WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1903 CA., PAMPHLETS (2) WITH AA (Box-folder 143-051)
- EXTRACTS OF STATEMENTS CONCERNING WALTER REED COMPILED AND PUBLISHED BY THE WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1903 CA., PAMPHLET (Box-folder 143-052)
- A VIRGINIANS WORK FOR CUBA 1904/04/30, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING WITH AA (Box-folder 143-053)
  [BALTIMORE SUN]
- IN MAJOR REEDS MEMORY - A SOCIETY FORMED TO ERECT MONUMENT TO VIRGINIAN 1904/04/30, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING WITH AA (Box-folder 143-054)
- MEMORIAL TO THE LATE MAJOR WALTER REED (MEDICAL RECORD) 1904/07/02, JOURNAL ARTICLE (Box-folder 143-055)
- A NOTABLE GATHERING 1904/10/21, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING WITH AA (Box-folder 143-056)
  BALTIMORE SUN
- LETTER FROM EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1905/01, FORM LETTER (Box-folder 143-057)
- LETTER FROM JOHN C. HEMMETER TO HOWARD A. KELLY 1907/10/22, ALS (Box-folder 143-058)
- ALBERT E. TRUBY - HOSPITAL, AMERICAN LAKE, WASHINGTON 1908, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 143-059)
- ALBERT E. TRUBY - HOSPITAL, AMERICAN LAKE, WASHINGTON 1908, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 143-060)
- LETTER FROM [ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE] TO JOHN C. HEMMETER 1913/02/02, TL (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 143-061)
- LETTER FROM ALBERT E. TRUBY TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1932/03/04, TL (CC) (Box-folder 143-062)
- NOTE CONCERNING MAJOR RAYMOND BRIGGS IN HAND OF JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1933/05/29, AN (Box-folder 143-063)
- COPY OF MEMORANDUM CONCERNING LAZEAR GENEALOGY 1935/11, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 143-064)
- LETTER FROM ALBERT E. TRUBY TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1936/04/27, TLS (P) WITH AA (Box-folder 143-065)
- TELEGRAM FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1940/05/12, TELEGRAM (Box-folder 144-001)
- TELEGRAM FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1940/05/12, TELEGRAM (CC) (Box-folder 144-002)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO HARRY H. DONNALLY 1940/08/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-003)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO EDITOR OF PUBLICATIONS OR LIBRARIAN 1940/08/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-004)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO EDITOR OF PUBLICATIONS OR LIBRARIAN 1940/08/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-005)
- LETTER FROM EDUARDO ANGELES TO F. DOMINGUEZ [IN SPANISH] 1940/09/08, TLS (P) (Box-folder 144-006)
- LETTER FROM EDUARDO ANGELES TO F. DOMINGUEZ [ENGLISH TRANSLATION] 1940/09/08, TL (Box-folder 144-007)
- LETTER FROM JOHN RUSSELL MASON TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1940/09/12, TLS (Box-folder 144-008)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JOHN RUSSELL MASON 1940/09/18, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-009)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JOHN RUSSELL MASON 1940/09/21, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-010)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO HARRY H. DONNALLY 1940/09/24, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-011)
- LETTER FROM JOHN RUSSELL MASON TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1940/09/25, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 144-012)
- LETTER FROM HARRY H. DONNALLY TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1940/09/26, TLS (Box-folder 144-013)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JOHN RUSSELL MASON 1940/09/30, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-014)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO HARRY H. DONNALLY 1940/10/01, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-015)
- NOTES RE: JAMES L. HANBERRY (IN HAND OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH) 1940S CA., 2 ANS (Box-folder 144-016)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - CONQUERORS OF YELLOW FEVER 1941/10, REPRINT (Box-folder 144-017)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - CONQUERORS OF YELLOW FEVER (WITH INSCRIPTION TO DR. FELIPE CARBONELL PONCE AND SIGNATURE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH) 1941/10, REPRINT WITH AA (Box-folder 144-018)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1941/11/27, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-019)
- LETTER FROM JAMES L. HANBERRY TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1941/12/08, ALS (Box-folder 144-020)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1941/12/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-021)
- LETTER FROM JAMES L. HANBERRY TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1941/12/21, ALS WITH ENVELOPE (Box-folder 144-022)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1942/01/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-023)
- LETTER FROM JAMES L. HANBERRY TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1942/02/16, ALS (Box-folder 144-024)
- LETTER FROM JAMES L. HANBERRY TO ALBERT E. TRUBY 1942/02/23, ALS (Box-folder 144-025)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1942/03/04, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-026)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1942/07/02, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-027)
- RECEIPT FOR PACKAGE FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1942/07/03, REGISTERED MAIL RECEIPT (Box-folder 144-028)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JAMES L. HANBERRY 1942/08/03, TL (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-029)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE F. HAIR TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1943/07/17, TPC WITH AA (Box-folder 144-030)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO GEORGE A. KELLOGG 1943/07/31, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-031)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO GEORGE F. HAIR 1943/08/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-032)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE F. HAIR TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1943/09/23, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 144-033)
- LETTER FROM JOSEPH F. SILER TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1945/12/15, TLS (Box-folder 144-034)
- LETTER FROM R. E. THOMASON TO WILLIAM M. BRUMBY 1946/05/07, TLS (P), NEGATIVE IMAGE (Box-folder 144-035)
- LETTER FROM JAMES M. HORAN TO TOM CONNALLY 1946/05/14, TLS WITH AA (P) (Box-folder 144-036)
- EXCERPTS FROM BIOGRAPHY OF GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG BY HIS WIFE 1946/05/16, TMS WITH AA (Box-folder 144-037)
- EXCERPTS FROM BIOGRAPHY OF GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG BY HIS WIFE 1946/05/16, TMS (CC) (Box-folder 144-038)
- EXCERPTS FROM BIOGRAPHY OF GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG BY HIS WIFE 1946/05/16, TMS (CC) (Box-folder 144-039)
- EXCERPTS FROM BIOGRAPHY OF GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG BY HIS WIFE 1946/05/16, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-040)
- EXCERPTS FROM BIOGRAPHY OF GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG BY HIS WIFE [WITH AUTOGRAPH ANNOTATIONS BY ALBERT E. TRUBY] 1946/05/16, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-041)
- LETTER FROM CHARLES WILSON TO R. E. THOMASON 1946/05/24, TL (P) (Box-folder 144-042)
- FAMILY OF DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR 1946/11, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-043)
- FAMILY OF DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR [ANNOTATED BY JANE L. GAWNE, DECEMBER 1954] 1946/11 [1954/12], TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-044)
- LETTER FROM JOSEPH F. SILER TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/11/01, TLS (Box-folder 144-045)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO COLONEL JOSEPH F. SILER 1946/11/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-046)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO COLONEL JOSEPH F. SILER 1946/11/15, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-047)
  CONCERNING MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR
- MINUTES OF THE ANNUAL MEETING OF THE BOARD OF MANAGERS, WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1946/11/21, TMS (CC) (Box-folder 144-048)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - TRANSCRIPT OF INTERVIEW WITH GENERAL LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED AND BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/11/21, TMS WITH AA (Box-folder 144-049)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - TRANSCRIPT OF INTERVIEW WITH GENERAL LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED AND BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/11/21, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-050)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - TRANSCRIPT OF INTERVIEW WITH GENERAL LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED AND BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/11/21, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-051)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - TRANSCRIPT OF INTERVIEW WITH GENERAL LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED AND BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1946/11/21, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-052)
- LETTER FROM ALBERT G. LOVE TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/11/22, ALS WITH AA (Box-folder 144-053)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO GENERAL ALBERT G. LOVE 1946/11/29, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-054)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO GENERAL ALBERT G. LOVE 1946/11/29, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-055)
- LETTER FROM IDA E. KISSINGER TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH, KISSINGER COLLECTION IN PERMANENT CARE AT CITY LIBRARY, COUPLE LEAVING 1946/12/05, CHRISTMAS CARD WITH AA AND EN. ALS, NEWSPAPER CLP. W/AA (Box-folder 144-056)
- LETTER FROM ALBERT G. LOVE TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/12/14, ALS (Box-folder 144-057)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO GENERAL ALBERT G. LOVE 1946/12/19, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-058)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO HANS W. IRELAND 1946/12/19, TL (CC) (Box-folder 144-059)
- LETTER FROM JOSEPH F. SILER TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/12/24, TLS (Box-folder 144-060)
- LETTER FROM ALBERT G. LOVE TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1946/12/26, ALS WITH AA (Box-folder 144-061)
- JOURNAL ARTICLE CITATIONS CONCERNING GENERAL GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1946 CA., 2 ANS (Box-folder 144-062)
- SPORTSMAN ON PARADE (PHILIP KAHLER HENCH) 1946 CA., NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) WITH AA (Box-folder 144-063)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO COLONEL JOSEPH F. SILER 1947/01/15, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-001)
- LETTER FROM WILLIAM H. WILBUR TO FRANCES B. SETH 1947/01/18, ALS (Box-folder 145-002)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO WILLIAM M. BRUMBY 1947/01/21, TL (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 145-003)
- LETTER FROM FRANCES B. SETH TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/01/23, TLS (Box-folder 145-004)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO FRANCES B. SETH 1947/01/28, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-005)
- LETTER FROM FRANCES B. SETH TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/01 CA., TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-006)
- LETTER FROM MARGARET LAZEAR BRIGGS TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/02/01, ALS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-007)
- FAMILY AND ANCESTORS OF DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR [GENEALOGICAL DIAGRAM] AND FAMILY OF DR. JESSE WILLIAM LAZEAR [ANNOTATED BY PEGGY BRIGGS] 1947/02/01, TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 145-008)
- LETTER FROM FRANCES B. SETH TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/02/04, TLS (Box-folder 145-009)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO COLONEL JOSEPH F. SILER 1947/02/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-010)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO FRANCES B. SETH 1947/02/10, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-011)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO FRANCES B. SETH 1947/02/19, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-012)
- LETTER FROM FRANCES B. SETH TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/02/25, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-013)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO FRANCES B. SETH 1947/03/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-014)
- LETTER FROM JOSEPH F. SILER TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/03/10, TLS (Box-folder 145-015)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO COLONEL JOSEPH F. SILER 1947/03/22, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-016)
- COPY OF MEMORANDUM CONCERNING THE LAZEAR GENEALOGY 1947/03/24, TMS (CC) (Box-folder 145-017)
- LETTER FROM PEDRO NOGUEIRA TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/04/22, TLS (Box-folder 145-018)
- LETTER FROM FRANCES B. SETH TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/05/05, TLS (Box-folder 145-019)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO FRANCES B. SETH 1947/05/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-020)
- LETTER FROM FRANCES B. SETH TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/05/15, TLS (Box-folder 145-021)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JOSE R. ANDREU 1947/05/16, TL (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 145-022)
- LETTER FROM PEDRO NOGUEIRA TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1947/09/13, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-023)
- LETTER FROM PEDRO NOGUEIRA TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1947/11/07, TLS WITH AA AND ENVELOPE (Box-folder 145-024)
- LETTER FROM PEDRO NOGUEIRA TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH [IN SPANISH] 1947/11/10, TLS (Box-folder 145-025)
- LETTER FROM PEDRO NOGUEIRA TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH [ENGLISH TRANSLATION] 1947/11/10, TL (Box-folder 145-026)
- LETTER FROM PEDRO NOGUEIRA TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1947/11/14, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-027)
- MINUTES OF THE ANNUAL MEETING OF THE BOARD OF MANAGERS, WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1947/11/25, TMS WITH TN (CC) (Box-folder 145-028)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO COLONEL JOSEPH F. SILER 1947/12/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-029)
- LAZEAR GENEALOGICAL INFORMATION 1947 CA., AMS (Box-folder 145-030)
- LAZEAR GENEALOGICAL INFORMATION 1947 CA., AMS (Box-folder 145-031)
- LAZEAR GENEALOGICAL INFORMATION 1947 CA., AMS (Box-folder 145-032)
- ANSWERS TO QUESTIONS IN LETTERS [CONCERNING LAZEAR GENEALOGY] 1947 CA., AMS (Box-folder 145-033)
- NOTES CONCERNING WILLIAM M. BRUMBY (IN HAND OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH) 1947 CA., AMS (Box-folder 145-034)
- NOTES CONCERNING LAZEAR GENEALOGY 1947 CA., 3 ANS (Box-folder 145-035)
- INFORMATION CONCERNING FAMILY OF DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR BY FRANCES B. SETH 1947 CA., TMS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-036)
- LAZEAR GENEALOGICAL INFORMATION 1947 CA., TMS (CC) (Box-folder 145-037)
- FAMILY AND ANCESTORS OF DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR [GENEALOGICAL DIAGRAM] 1947 CA., TMS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-038)
- FAMILY AND ANCESTORS OF DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR [GENEALOGICAL DIAGRAM] 1947 CA., TMS (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 145-039)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO ALBERT E. TRUBY [ANNOTATED BY ALBERT E. TRUBY] 1948/01/09, TLS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-040)
- LETTER FROM THELMA MARTENS REPETTI TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1948/01/25, ALS (Box-folder 145-041)
- LETTER FROM RITA FOWLER TO THELMA MARTENS REPETTI [1948]/01/29, ALS (Box-folder 145-042)
- LETTER FROM ALBERT E. TRUBY TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1948/01 CA., ALS WITH ENVELOPE (Box-folder 145-043)
- LIST OF TRANSPORT ARRIVALS AND DEPARTURES, HAVANA, CUBA, JULY 1 1900 - JUNE 30 1901 [ANNOTATED BY ALBERT E. TRUBY] 1948/01 CA., PRINTED FORM WITH AA (Box-folder 145-044)
- LETTER FROM THELMA MARTENS REPETTI TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1948/02/08, ALS (Box-folder 145-045)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO PEDRO NOGUEIRA 1948/02/12, TL (CC) WITH AA (Box-folder 145-046)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO THELMA MARTENS REPETTI 1948/02/17, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-047)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO MRS RITA FOWLER 1948/02/19, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-048)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - CONFIDENTIAL MEMORANDUM OF TRIP TO CUBA 1948/03/02-11, TMS WITH AA (Box-folder 145-049)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JOHN J. MORAN 1948/03/25, TL (CC) (Box-folder 145-050)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO PEDRO NOGUEIRA 1948/03/25, TL (CC) AN (Box-folder 145-051)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO FELIPE CARBONELL 1948/03/25, TL (CC) WITH 2 ANS (Box-folder 145-052)